Hello friends, welcome to Tips.
Whenever we want to buy a health insurance policy,
many questions come to our mind.
One of the most important questions is which
health insurance company should we buy the best health policy from, which
gives us timely approval, whose plan is affordable,
meaning we can afford it considering our financial situation. For
this type of insurance,
we need a good insurance company. So,
in today's video, I have
brought you five such insurance companies. I am going to
tell you about them in full detail. Keeping
all these questions in mind, today
I have made this video. In this video, I am going to
tell you about the top five insurance companies
and by looking at them, you can purchase a good
plan. So, in this video,
I am going to tell you about five insurance companies in full detail. So,
let's
start the video.
[Music]
When we buy a policy from a good health insurance company, there are
many
benefits. Firstly, we get timely
approval. Second, we do
not have to bear any financial burden. Thirdly, we
can get treatment in our nearest hospital
where he is  The hospital should be
in the panel list of the insurance company, which means its
network hospital, the
hospital where I have to get my treatment should also be in the list, so there are
many benefits,
keeping these benefits in mind, today I am going to
tell you about five insurance companies, in this the first
insurance company is HDFC,
five companies in
India are in the network of 12000 hospitals,
what is that
98.49 percent out of hundred means out of 100 they
pass so many percent claims and
reject the rest, whatever the reason may be, they will
tell at this time,
apart from this, if you want to get more information about this insurance company
or
you want to select a plan, then
I have also mentioned this contact number on it, so
you can contact on this and
talk directly to the toll free number, if it is
not toll free then if you talk on the P number
then you will get the response from there,
after that
when we contact any hospital  If you are admitted under the
insurance company, then the approval time will be different for every insurance
company. So the
time period of HDFC EGO is
between one to two hours.
What is the maximum time that
we get from the insurance company on HDFC time?
When the final bill is
sent by the hospital to the insurance company, they
approve it within an hour. So, it is a
different matter if it takes 3 hours or any additional
time, the
turnaround time is between one to two hours.
Okay, this is the first one.
In the big list of HDFC EGO, the second one is ICC Lombard.
ICC Lombard has
more than 7500 network hospitals and
its claim ratio is
97.09%. That means
its claim ratio is 97.09% out of 100. The
remaining 3%, something like
2.91, goes into its dinner or
whatever it is or reimbursement.  It
is different and
I have
also provided toll free numbers for their claim 7.09 percent. If you want to
purchase any insurance policy, you
can discuss its plan in detail
and if you have any other questions, you
can talk to the insurance company directly. This is a toll
free number and its approval time is
8600 in the hospital network of Reliance General.
After this, its claim ratio is
98.65. You
can do your plan by doing this
and discuss any question in the hospital. Its
track time, which is the approval
time, is between one hour to four hours.
So this is also a very good company.
You can also see its plans separately
on their website. If there is
a nearby agent, you
can contact him also. After that, the fourth number
comes up is of Bajaj Insurance Company.
It is 6500 and
its claim ratio is 96.59
percent. I have provided its contact number also,
toll free.  There is a number on this number, you
can get more information by talking to it, about the health
insurance policy, about the plan
or if you have any other question,
you can discuss it there. Its tight
time is one hour, one and the other.
After that, the fifth company is
Future Generali, its network
hospital is more than 8000, its
clutch show is
96.01%, I have given its contact number also, it is a
toll free number, you can call on this number and find out about the
plan and
purchase your health policy,
and its time is between one hour to
four hours,
I have told you about these 5 health insurance companies,
you can choose the plan of any of these for yourself and
your family, you
can also buy this policy
from their website, there is a
separate portal online, you can buy from there
or if you have an agent nearby, you
can also buy from him, I would suggest you to
buy from an agent,
buy from any agent near you so that you  If you do
not face any problem while taking the claim, then this is all
in today's video, we will meet
in the next video. If
you like the video, then like the video, comment and
definitely subscribe to the channel. See you
in the next video, till then, goodbye.